Gabriel A Zepeda

My goal is to gain experience and utilize my communication, technical, and organizational skills in all areas of my life. I have a strong willingness to learn and always willing to take on opportunities and tackle any challenge head on.

Qualifications

- Have ran a business home renovationg which has given me a good eye for organization and planning from start to finish.
- From my time in university I have studied electrical circuits with respect to modern power systems
 as well as signals and systems.
- Well versed in software & hardware components especially when fixing and or assembling computer systems.
- Properly utilize computer programming languages such as HTML, XML CSS, Java, Python, SQL, and PL/SQL.

Education

University of Connecticut, Storrs CT

Four years towards a Bachelors in Electrical Engineering degree.

Have taken various computer science courses such as Java, Python, and Matlab.

Norwalk Community College, Norwalk CT

Majored in Computer Science

Took related Computer Science Courses:

- Web Development & Design I & II Through objective based and team projects I am learning Advanced HTML, XML, CSS, and Javascript techniques.
- Database Development I & II Learning SQL and PL/SQL programming languages.
- Internet Commerce Technology Covers emerging online technologies and trends and their influence on the electronic marketplace.
- Intro to Software Applications A course which focuses on teaching simple basics such as using both Apple and Windows computers, Windows Office Applications as well as many other useful computer programs the student might encounter within an office setting.

Work Experience

November 2011 - August 2014

ShopRite - Stamford, CT

Helped customers with any questions or concerns they might have giving me a solid background in customer service gained during my high school years.

January 2015 - December 2015

University of Connecticut - Storrs CT

Worked with staff on our campus dining hall giving me a strong ability to work under time constraints preparing for breakfast, lunch, or dinner switches. Also an ability to be cleanly and professional.

April 2017 - May 2017

Norwalk Community College - Norwalk, CT

Worked with my fellow students on a team to create a website for NECA (Norwalk Early College Academy), an IBM funded program geared towards providing Norwalk HS students a free college education.

http://neca.bright-moments.com/

January 2018 - January 2021

HomeDepot - Stamford CT - (203) 905-6400

Worked at the Pro Desk hand in hand with building contractors making sure that they received the materials they needed for their building projects. It was necessary to familiarize myself with the HD system in order to create, pull, and finalize requested orders.

January 2021 - November 2023

Freelance / Self Employed

Home Renovator – Carpentry / Framing / Sheetrocking / Sanding / Painting / Appliance Installations / Landscaping.

Related Experience

- Member of Avid (Advancement via Individial Determination) and Success Program during Highschool. August 2009 – June 2013
- IEEE (Institute for Electrical and Electronic Engineering) Club 2014
- Attended Computer Programming and autonomous machine building seminars.
- Very tech savy, familiarizing myself with fixing any softrware or hardware computer issue.
- Have taken public speaking courses which has helped give me experience in presenting.
- Good organizational skills gained during my self employment work.